Sanjana Gajanana Shetty

Sanjanags12 |in sanjana-shetty-gs12 | \bigoplus My Portfolio | \searrow sanjanashetty919@gmail.com |+919483202522

SUMMARY

I am an Enthusiastic learner, there is always a curiosity that lies in me to learn new things. To use and develop my skills and knowledge for the growth of an organization; to gain experience in the industrial area and polish my technical skills; to persevere towards attaining a respective position in the organization.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Associate Consultant (UI/UX Developer)-Optivalue Tek Consulting

Dec 2023 - Present

Designed and developed user interfaces for a job portal project inclueds timesheet, utilizing React for dynamic UI rendering. Currently spearheading frontend development efforts using React, TypeScript, and Tailwind CSS. Integrated APIs seamlessly to enhance user experience and functionality. Implemented recruiter model registration and signup functionalities. Implemented front end for the entire hire-acontractor module and co-ordinator module and also worked on candidate module. Worked on company website using NextJs. Tech stacks used: ReactJs, Javascript, Typescript, Tailwindess, NextJs

Core Engineering Development- Trainee Consultant

Feb 2023 - Nov 2023

Led data pre-processing initiatives to ensure data quality and consistency for analysis. Contributed to the development of Optimatch core engineering solutions, leveraging Neo4j for optimized data querying and management. Tech stack: Python, Neo4j, MySQL

PROJECTS

Voice based Library Management System (VBLMS)

Link to git

VBLMS is a project developed using Django, to help students, librarians in redesigning the traditional library system with the touch of digital technology. Bootstrap framework is also used to speed up UI development. Skills acquired: HTML, CSS, Java, DBMS, Django

Personal Portfolio Link to git

Developed a personal portfolio showcasing my work, utilizing HTML, CSS, and JavaScript to create a responsive and visually appealing web experience. Demonstrated strong front-end development skills through custom design and interactive features.

EDUCATION

2018 - 2022	BE (ISE) at BMSIT and M, Bengaluru	(GPA: 8.36/10.0)
2018	Class 12th Karnataka PUE	(82.17)
2016	Class 10th Karnataka State Board	(95.84)

SKILLS

Programming Languages: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Python

Front-end Technologies: React, NextJs, TypeScript, Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS

Back-end Technologies: Django , Flask DataBase Management: Neo4j, Mysql

Version Control: Git

SKILLS

Music, Painting, badminton Kannada, English, Hindi